Janvi is with us.  Good morning Janvi.   First of all,
what are the December quarter results and IPO updates?  Give me those details.
Absolutely good morning.  Let's start with the results.
ICICI Lombard results came out yesterday
after the market closed. The results seem to be a bit
mixed.  The company's
PAT here is weaker than expected.
If we look at it, due to higher operating expenses,
weakness seems to be coming here.
If we look at the premium earnings of the company, it
seems to be increasing by 13% to around Rs 5685 crore.  If we look at the profits, there is a
decline of up to 9%.  The estimate was Rs 850
crore.  If we look at it, the
company has recorded a profit of Rs 659 crore.
So here comes a slightly predictably weak Pat.
But looking at the overall numbers,
if we look at the combined gross return premium, there is a
15% increase here.
Looking at the solvency ratio of the company, it has come down from 273% to 269%.
And if we look at the combined ratio, it
seems to be increasing from 102.7% to 104.5%.
Tata Alexi: If we talk about its numbers, then
if we look at the operational numbers, they are
looking quite good.  The company's
revenue has increased by about 4%.
This company has registered assets of Rs 953 crore.
If we talk about the EBITDA of the company, then here we see an increase of 16%, the
estimate was Rs 180 crore.  Ah,
if you look at it, it appears to be coming for Rs 198 crore.
So the numbers here are
operationally quite good.  Margin: The company has
expanded well.
Margins of 18.5% are seen expanding to 20.8%.
So here's what to keep an eye on.
If we talk about yesterday, there were two numbers from cash also
after the market closed, in which if we talk about 5 paisa
digital, then the
numbers here are looking a little weak.  The company's
revenue has declined by 7%.
If we look at the operating profits, there is a decline of 11%.
Margins have contracted slightly.
Margins of 34.9% came down to 33.5%.  Profits
also seem to be declining.  So
overall weak numbers are presented here.
Just Dial: Talking about its numbers, there are
a bit of mixed numbers on the front here.
If we look at it from a working point of view, the
numbers are quite good.  The company's revenue
appears to be flattening.  There is a gain of about 1%
here.  But if we talk about margins, the
margins of 28% have come down to 3.3%.  The
company's profit has declined by 1.5%.
So there's a bit of a mixed set of numbers here.  If we
talk about IPO updates, then
Amgi Media Labs' IPO was
opened yesterday.  Was.  Talking about today's Day One update, the
total is 6% full so far.  Retail
subscription is seen coming at 28%.
Talking about Bharat Cooking Coal's IPO, the
IPO has closed yesterday and a very strong
subscription has been received here.
If we look at the total, the company's
IPO has been subscribed approximately 146 times.  The
QIB portion was seen filled 310 times
and if we look at the retail portion, it was
filled 49.3 times.
This is the IPO that has seen the highest retail subscription till date.
Absolutely.  Now let us understand from you Janvi
which news is going to be in the headlines today
and what will be the important triggers for the market
in the setup.
Absolutely, if we start with today's news,
Infosys results are going to come
after the market closes, so we have to keep an eye on this.
HDFC AMC Union Bank Its numbers will be
seen coming from FNO.  So both these counters have to be
kept under observation.  Bajaj Auto will launch its new
electric two-wheeler today
under the Bajaj Chetak brand.  It is going to be
considered in the Spark Board meeting.   The
company will consider raising funds through a preferential issue and
this merger will be seen taking place after the merger of Alcaro Logistics with its subsidiaries, which is about 51.5 crore shares of the company that will be listed today.  The
ex-date is the date of Kotak
Mahindra Bank stock split. The
face value of the split stock will
decrease from five to one.  So
it will appear split in the ratio of 1:5.
Anchor lock in is about to open for Park Medi
Mediar's Nephro Care Service.  So, you have to keep an
eye on the news here, Polycab can be a
block deal of around Rs 1200 crores,
if you look at the domestic mutual fund,
you can sell some part of it, the floor price which has been
fixed is around Rs 7300, which is
currently shown at a discount of more than 20% from the current price, internally, you have to
keep the focus here that the
company has given clarification on the news of removal of 10 minute delivery.  The
company said that at present no such
development has been seen coming to the company from the government.
So here's the
update.  Lloyd Energy Works Company has
signed an agreement with Material Works, a US company, for the
global commercial rights of Ecop Technology. The
company has been seen receiving an LOI of Rs 130 crore from Interage Building Products. And finally,
if we look at the red tape, yesterday there were reports in the
market that the founder of Black Stone
may sell some of his stake, then the
company clarified that the
founder has no such idea at present and no further talks are going on at present.
Thank you Janvia.